# **Tran Trung Kien**

Dec 28, 1993

kientrancm@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kientranvn

www.fb.com/kientrancm

Phone: +84 88881 5552

333/7A Le Van Sy Street, Ward 1, Tan Binh District, HCMC, Vietnam



# **PERSONAL STATEMENT**

I have 3 years of experience as Embedded Software Test Engineer. Ability to quickly adapt to different project environments, work well independently and as part of a team. Ability to prioritize tasks and meet deadlines. Experience with unit testing, system testing and generated test reports. Experienced over automotive testing tools that include RTRT, Vector Cast, Canoe. Report and track the issues using ALM, Clear-case, ClearQuest, HP QC. Experienced with requirement specifications and changing requirement sheets using IBM DOORS tool.

- \* Proactively, honestly, self-motivation, like challenging, willing to take responsibility.
- \* Worked on-site in India and willing to work on-site for short, long term.
- \* Experienced in on-site working for international company and stakeholders.
- \* Work-life integration styles.

#### **EDUCATION**

Sep 2011 – July 2015 Can Tho University

Major is Computer Engineering - Grade: 3.0/4.0

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **MDN SAVIWAVE Ltd**

32 Ton That Tung, District 1, HCMC

# **Software Test Engineer**

July 2015 - October 2016

- Validate embedded software (RTOS, GSM)
- Design and implement automation test script
- Execute test case and analyse test report
- Open AT Platform, Python, HP Quality Center

# Robert Bosch Engineering and Business Solution Vietnam

364 Cong Hoa Street, Tan Binh District, HCMC

# **Automotive Embedded Software Test Engineer**

November 2016 – Present

- Implement unit testing
- Worked on-site in India 8 months.
- 5 projects
- Unit testing
- Customer: German, Indian

### **Team Coordinator**

October 2018 – Present

- Project coordinator between Vietnam team and customer, stakeholders.
- Mentor, training for new team member

<u>Organizer</u> - Come to Suburb 2016 and 2017 - Thanh Loc Ward, District 12, HCMC Dec 2016 - Dec 2017

Organize activities and support facilities for children. Host the knowledge contest "Ring the Golden Bell". Clean up the polluted channels and streets in Thanh Loc Ward.

## **PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES**

- The degree of engineer: Computer Engineering
- TIIC MCU Design Contest 2014 Texas Instrument
- Volunteer of Learning Resource Center at CTU (2011 2015)
- Success through superior professionalism (23 October 2017)
- BMI Hackathon in Robert Bosch Engineering and Business Solution Vietnam (November 2018)

# **KEY SKILLS**

#### Skills

- Strong in software testing skills, testing techniques
- Good English communication skills
- Analytical and problem-solving
- Debugging
- The ability to learn quickly
- Teamwork
- ISO26262, ISTQB, ASPICE, AGILE

# **Programming Language**

- Strong in C programming for Embedded Software
- PTU script language in RTRT
- Python Script
- Open AT Platform
- C#

# Micro-controller

- Raspberry Pi 2, Galileo Intel, Arduino, MSP430, Nuvoton NUC140, SIM900, ZigBee
- Sensor(HMC5883L, MPU6050, Temperature, pH, Oxygen)

# IDE

- RTRT Rational Test Real Time
- Clear-Case, AEEE, DOOR, ClearQuest, RADAR, ALM, HP Quality Center
- Arduino IDE, Galileo IDE

# **PERSONAL INTERESTS**

Traveling | Eating | Reading | Fashion